Office of Communications and Marketing Records UA252
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Faculty files, 1946 -- 2018; UA252.005; 18 Linear Feet
  - Taylor, Allen (Nutrition), 1985-06-25 -- 2000; UA252.005.030.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - Taylor, Holly (Psychology), 1994-11-14 -- 2004; UA252.005.030.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 80)
  - Taylor, Jacqueline (Philosophy), 1995; UA252.005.030.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 81)
  - Taylor, Rosemary C.R. [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1981-05-06 -- 2002; UA252.005.030.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 82)
  - Taylor, Vivian, 1981-06-10 -- 1985-11-14; UA252.005.030.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 83)
  - Teichman, Sherman (Faculty & Staff), 1986-02-18 -- 2003; UA252.005.030.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 84)
  - Tensa, Dr. Joseph I. (Faculty and Staff), 1985 -- 1987-09-06; UA252.005.030.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 85)
  - Teres, Dr. Daniel (Medical), 1991-09; UA252.005.030.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 86)
  - Terry, Sarah M. [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1980-09-26 -- 1986-08-28; UA252.005.030.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - Terkla, Dawn Geronimo (Management/Planning), 1987-07-16 -- 1987-12-03; UA252.005.030.00088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 88)
  - Tesini, Dr. David (Faculty & Staff), 1985-03-13 -- 1985-10-14; UA252.005.030.00089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 89)
  - Theoharides, Theoharis, 1987-07-30 -- 2005; UA252.005.030.00090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 90)
  - Thompson, Dr. Scott W. [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1977-02 -- 1997-05-19; UA252.005.030.00091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30, Folder 91)
  - Thornton, Ronald K. [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1981-02-16 -- 1992; UA252.005.031.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Tilger, Justine (Faculty and Staff), 1986-08-27; UA252.005.031.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Tillotson, James (Nutrition), 1989-06 -- 2002; UA252.005.031.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Tobin, Roger (Physics), 1995; UA252.005.031.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Toole, Bryan, 1987-01-15 -- 1987-11-19; UA252.005.031.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Tornatzky, Walter (Psychology), 1990-11; UA252.005.031.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Torres, Antonio (UEP ++), 1997-12; UA252.005.031.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Towers, Sara (Dental), 2001; UA252.005.031.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Trefethen, Lloyd M., 1958-12 -- 1989-05-01; UA252.005.031.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Trepagnier, Dr. Cheryl Goodenough, 1990 -- 1991; UA252.005.031.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Trexler, Alice [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1980-11 -- 1988-09; UA252.005.031.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Trimmer, Barry (Biology), 1991 -- 2007-01-25; UA252.005.031.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Tringale, Maria (Advancement), 2004; UA252.005.031.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Troen, Aaron (Nutrition), 2002; UA252.005.031.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Trout, Dennnis (Classics), 1997-04; UA252.005.031.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Tsamtsouris, Dr. Anthi (Facultry and Staff), 1986-08-27 -- 1989; UA252.005.031.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Tsutsumi, Kentaro (Civil Eng.), 1963 -- 1987-02-12; UA252.005.031.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Tucker, Katherine (Nutrition), 1996-12-10 -- 1997; UA252.005.031.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Tzipori, Dr. Saul (Vet School), 1992; UA252.005.031.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Ucci, Dr. Angelo (Medical), 1991; UA252.005.031.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Ueda, Reed [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1983-02-10 -- 1990; UA252.005.031.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Uhlir, Arthur Jr., 1970-12 -- 1986-10-09; UA252.005.031.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Uhrig, R. Miles (Faculty & Staff), 1966-05-17 -- 2008-03-18; UA252.005.031.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Urry, Dr. Grant W. (Chairman of Chemistry), 1965 -- 1977-09-29; UA252.005.031.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Usher, Joe (Veterinary School), 1989-09; UA252.005.031.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Utz, Arthur L. (Chemistry), 1994-11-14; UA252.005.031.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Vaaler, Paul (Fletcher), 1996; UA252.005.031.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Valaes, Timos (Medical School), 1989; UA252.005.031.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Vancamp, Rosemarie (Faculty and Staff), 1985-09 -- 1991; UA252.005.031.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Van Sant, Anne Prof. (English), 1988-05 -- 1997; UA252.005.031.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Vannah, Dr. Bill (Medical School), 1991; UA252.005.031.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Veremis, Thanos (Fletcher), 2001-08-07 -- 2001-09-10; UA252.005.031.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Vergo, Dr. Thomas (Faculty and Staff), 1983-03-07 -- 1991; UA252.005.031.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Versluys, Hilda (BSOT), 1990-11; UA252.005.031.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Vilenkin, Alexander (Faculty and Staff), 1983-06 -- 1996; UA252.005.031.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Vinger, Paul (Medical), 1997-01-06; UA252.005.031.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Vo, Van Toi [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1987-04-09 -- 1995-10; UA252.005.031.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Vogel, Richard (Faculty and Staff), 1986-12-04 -- 1997-07-25; UA252.005.031.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Von Lazar, Arped (Faculty and Staff), 1969-03-16 -- 1997-04; UA252.005.031.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Von Moltke, Lisa (Medical School), 1994-01; UA252.005.031.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Wachman, Alan (Fletcher), 1996; UA252.005.031.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Waggener, Thomas B. (Medical School), 1990-05 -- 1991-10; UA252.005.031.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Wagner, Dr. Pam (Vet. Medicince), 1991; UA252.005.031.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Wagner, Dr. Richard (Faculty and Staff), 1986-08-19; UA252.005.031.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Waldau, Paul (Veterinary), 2005; UA252.005.031.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Waldor, Matthew (Medicine), 1998-10; UA252.005.031.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Walid, Dr. (Dental School), 1992; UA252.005.031.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Walker, Peter (Nutrition), 2002; UA252.005.031.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Waller, Bill (Physics), 1997; UA252.005.031.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Walser, Joseph (Religion), 1998 -- 1999-03; UA252.005.031.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Walt, Dr. David (Liberal Arts/Engineer), 1987-04-20 -- 1998-07-06; UA252.005.031.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Wandle, Caroline (Education), 1990-11; UA252.005.031.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Wang, Paul (Medical), 1998; UA252.005.031.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Wang, Xiang-Dong (Nutrition), 2000; UA252.005.031.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Ware, John E. Jr. (Medical School), 1996; UA252.005.031.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Wartenberg, Dr. Allan (Medical School), 1992; UA252.005.031.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Weaver, David (Physics), 1964-12-28 -- 1982-11; UA252.005.031.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Webb, Patrick (Nutrition), 1999; UA252.005.031.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Wechsler, Judith [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1980-10-30 -- 1990-05; UA252.005.031.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Willson, Robert F.(Atronomy Dept.), 1991-02 -- 2003; UA252.005.031.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Wilson, Jonathan [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1982-12-31 -- 1995-08-23; UA252.005.031.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Wingwood, Harold (Faculty and Staff), 1984; UA252.005.031.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Winn, Peter, 1982-04-29 -- 1992; UA252.005.031.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - Winter, Stephen, 1971-10-15 -- 1989-12; UA252.005.031.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 64)
  - Wishik, Heather (TLGBC), 1993; UA252.005.031.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 65)
  - Wolf, Maryanne (Faculty), 1982-11-12 -- 2003; UA252.005.031.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 66)
  - Wolfe, Dr. Hubert (Medical School), 1987; UA252.005.031.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - Wolfe, Dr. Jessica (Medical), 1989; UA252.005.031.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - Wolkowicz, Dr. John (Dental), 1989; UA252.005.031.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 69)
  - Woodin, Mark (Civil Engineering), 1999-02; UA252.005.031.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 70)
  - Woods, Margo, 1996-09-25; UA252.005.031.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 71)
  - Woodward, Dr. Alan (Community health), 1990-05; UA252.005.031.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 72)
  - Wortis, Henry H. (Faculty and Staff), 1983-06 -- 1996; UA252.005.031.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 73)
  - Wright, Andrew (Faculty), 1990-04 -- 1997; UA252.005.031.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 74)
  - Wright, Dorice (Liberal Arts), 1993; UA252.005.031.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 75)
  - Wurm, Dr. Heinrich (Faculty and Staff), 1983-06-06 -- 1983-09-07; UA252.005.031.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 76)
  - Wynes, David (Faculty and Staff), 1987-01-15; UA252.005.031.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 77)
  - Bacow, Lawrence, 2001-05-09 -- 2010-05-11; UA252.005.031.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 78)
  - Baise, Launie, 2008-02; UA252.005.031.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 79)
  - Baskins, Cristelle, 2008-05-07 -- 2009-01-06; UA252.005.031.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 80)
  - Bauer, Nancy, 2004-08-22 -- 2005-07-18; UA252.005.031.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 81)
  - Bayne, Sheila, 2007-09-19 -- 2007-12-11; UA252.005.031.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 82)
  - Bedau, Hugo, 2005-02-23 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.031.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 83)
  - Bell, Doug, 2003-06-20; UA252.005.031.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 84)
  - Berstein, Mel, 2000-10-11 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.031.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 85)
  - Berry, Jeffrey, 2000-04-24 -- 2009-04-01; UA252.005.032.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Carzo, Rocky, 1999 -- 2005; UA252.005.032.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 2)
    newspaper clippings/online articles/obituary/event program
  - Caviness, Madeline, 2002 -- 2007; UA252.005.032.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Cebe, Peggy, 2004 -- 2005; UA252.005.032.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Chapra, Steve, 2000 -- 2005; UA252.005.032.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 5)
    press release/academic paper/faculty guide profile
  - Chaisson, Eric, 2002 -- 2009; UA252.005.032.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 6)
    online articles/biographical sketch/newspaper clippings
  - Clark, Andrew, 2007; UA252.005.032.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Coffin, Lee, 2003; UA252.005.032.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 8)
    resume/memo/online Tufts articles
  - Cook, Robert, 2000 -- 2002; UA252.005.032.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 9)
    curriculum vitae/book chapter/Tufts journal article/lab write-up
  - Crane, Gregory, 1996 -- 2009; UA252.005.032.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 10)
    project notes/press releases/emails/meeting notes/Tufts journal article/academic paper
  - Doughtie, Mark, 2005; UA252.005.032.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 11)
    faculty profile
  - Dow, James, 2004; UA252.005.032.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Downing, Michael, 2005; UA252.005.032.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 13)
    faculty guide profile
  - Drachman, Virginia, 2002 -- 2005; UA252.005.032.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 14)
    faculty profile/book notes/event invitation
  - Dwyer, Johanna, 2003; UA252.005.032.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Easterbrooks, Anne, 2004 -- 2005; UA252.005.032.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 16)
    curriculum vitae/faculty guide profile
  - Eichenberg, Richard, 2000 -- 2005; UA252.005.032.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 17)
    emails/faculty profile/study summary/faxes/academic papers/Academic paper abstract/tables and graphs/media advisory
  - Elkind, David, 2005; UA252.005.032.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Ernst, Susan, 2002 -- 2005; UA252.005.032.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 19)
    faculty guide profile/resume/graphs
  - Fantini, Sergio, 2003; UA252.005.032.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 20)
    curriculum vitae
  - Feldman, David Henry, 2005; UA252.005.032.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Flytzani-Stephanopoulis, M., 2005; UA252.005.032.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Fultz, Jack, 2002; UA252.005.032.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Gantcher, Nathan, 2005; UA252.005.032.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 24)
    list/faculty guide profile
  - Garlick, Jonathan, 2012; UA252.005.032.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 25)
    freshman seminar student op-eds
  - Gill, Gerald, 2007; UA252.005.032.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 26)
    funeral program
  - Gittleman, Sol, 1998 -- 2005; UA252.005.032.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 27)
    biographical sketch/resume/press releases/media list/emails/notes/biography/course description/online articles/faculty profile
  - Glaser, James, 2002 -- 2009; UA252.005.032.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 28)
    press release/academic paper/emails/faculty profile
  - Dobrow, Julie, 2005-07-15 -- 2010-07-28; UA252.005.032.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Diggs, Deborah, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - DiBaggio, John, 2001-06-07 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Der Manuelian, Lucy, 1985 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Dennett, Daniel, 2005-01-06 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Cuttino, David, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Dane, Ben, 2002-02-06 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Goldman, Michael, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Gonsalves, Robert, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Goodwin, Neva, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Gopin, Marc (Facutlty), 2002-04-09 -- 2005-08-12; UA252.005.032.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Gute, David, 2006-01-19 -- 2006-01-24; UA252.005.032.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Haefeli, Evan, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Hahn, Tomie, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Hitchner, Bruce, 2005-02-16 -- 2005-09-07; UA252.005.032.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Jalal, Ayesha, 2001-10-22; UA252.005.032.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Jeka, Mary, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Jennings, James, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Kaiser-Lenoir, Claudia, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Kaplan, David, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Kirshen, Paul, 2002-05-30 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Kouguell, Susan, 2005-07-22; UA252.005.032.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Kounaves, Sam, 2002-03-22 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Krimsky, Sheldon, 2001-04-24 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Lang, Kenneth, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Lerner, Richard, 2000-03 -- 2007-01-28; UA252.005.032.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Lester, Joan (Faculty), 2002-09-04 -- 2005-08-12; UA252.005.032.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Leupp, Gary, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Levin, Michael, 2013-08-25; UA252.005.032.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Lewis, Kim, 2001-05-23 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Locke, David, 2005-07-22; UA252.005.032.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - Maddox, Keith, 2002-01-29 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - Manz, Beatrice, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - Matson, Doug, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - McCusker, Daniel, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - McDonald, John, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - McMillan, Margaret, 2001-10-14 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Mead, Molly, 2001-08 -- 2005-08-12; UA252.005.032.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Meser, Ellen, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - Metcalf, Gilbert, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Miaoulis, ionnis, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - Miczek, Klaus, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Miller, Neil, 2005-07-22; UA252.005.032.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - Mufti, Malik, 2001-10-22; UA252.005.032.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - President's General 1990's, 1999-06-16 -- 1999-12-01; UA252.005.032.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - Mumme, Donna, 2003-01-21 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - Munoz, Vincent, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - Newby, P.K., 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - Norman, George, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - O'Leary, David, 2005-07-15 -- 2006-12-29; UA252.005.032.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 78)
  - Olum, Ken, 2005-07-18 -- 2005-07-25; UA252.005.032.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 79)
  - Ostrander, Susan, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 80)
  - Panetta, Karen, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 81)
  - Penvenne, Jeanne, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 82)
  - Portney, Kent, 2001-10-12 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 83)
  - Retsinas, John, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 84)
  - Robinson, Pearl, 2001-11-06 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 85)
  - Rogers, Chris, 2002-07-03 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 86)
  - Rothbaum, Fred, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 87)
  - Saperstein, George, 2005-08-12; UA252.005.032.00088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 88)
  - Scarlett, George, 2001-12-12 -- 2005-08-04; UA252.005.032.00089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 89)
  - Schlegel, Amy, 2003-12-16 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 90)
  - Senelick, Laurence, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 91)
  - Shaw, Rosalind, 2003-01-30; UA252.005.032.00092; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 92)
  - Sherwin, Martin, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00093; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 93)
  - Smith, George, 2005-07-15 -- 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00094; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 94)
  - Sommers, Samuel, 2006-11-30 -- 2008-10-20; UA252.005.032.00095; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 95)
  - Sorachi, Salvatore, 2001-12-27 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00096; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 96)
  - Spivak, Howard, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00097; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 97)
  - Sternberg, Robert, 2005-07-14; UA252.005.032.00098; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 98)
  - Summit, Jeffrey, 2005-07-13 -- 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00099; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 99)
  - Sykes, Charles, 2006 -- 2009-06-02; UA252.005.032.00100; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 100)
  - Taylor, Holly, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00101; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 101)
  - Tobin, Roger, 2007-09-19; UA252.005.032.00102; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 102)
  - Trimmer, Barry, 2001-06-29 -- 2010-07-01; UA252.005.032.00103; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 103)
  - Tynan, Mely, 2005-07-14; UA252.005.032.00104; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 104)
  - Vandenberg, Laura, 2011-06-28; UA252.005.032.00105; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 105)
  - Waller, William H., 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00106; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 106)
  - Walt, David, 2005-07-15 -- 2006-03-14; UA252.005.032.00107; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 107)
  - Wertlieb, Donald, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00108; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 108)
  - Wilson, Jonathan, 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00109; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 109)
  - Wolf, Maryanne, 2002-03-18 -- 2005-07-15; UA252.005.032.00110; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 110)
  - York, Doris, 2005-11-29 -- 2005-12-23; UA252.005.032.00111; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 111)
  - Zeller, Janet, 2005-07-18; UA252.005.032.00112; 1 Folder(s) (Box 32, Folder 112)
  - Gerald Gill, "Another Light on the Hill", circa 2001; UA252.002122 (Box 32, Folder 113)
    Transferred by Office of Communications and Marketing, 2019, UA-2020-058.
- Videos, 1991 -- 2016; UA252.006; 4.8 Linear Feet; 15 Digital Object(s); 2.35 Gigabytes
  This series contains VHS tapes, beta tapes, CDs, DVDs, and digital videos of Tufts events or events featuring members of the Tufts community. Item titles were provided by the Office of Communications and Marketing.
  - Tufts Letterman, undated; UA252.006.033.00001; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Bubs on Letterman (Original), undated; UA252.006.033.00002; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Beezlebubs on David Letterman WBZ - Studying Abroad, undated; UA252.006.033.00003; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Leila Fawaz, Tufts University, 2003-03-05; UA252.006.033.00004; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - A Jumbo Celebration, 2001-08-24; UA252.006.033.00005; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Films for Social Change, undated; UA252.006.033.00006; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Daniel Dennett, Tufts University, 2003-09-16; UA252.006.033.00007; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Rich Learner - What Kids Ned to Succeed, 2003-08-08; UA252.006.033.00008; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Knorpel Knochen & Co Organe aus dem Reagenzglas, undated; UA252.006.033.00009; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Tufts University Commencement 2007 Medford/Somerville, UA252.006.033.00010; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Tufts Commencement 2011, UA252.006.033.00011; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - SP Master, undated; UA252.006.033.00012; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Keeping Kids on Track 5 Moments Amazing Young People, undated; UA252.006.033.00013; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Tufts University Commencement 2006, 2006-05-21; UA252.006.033.00014; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - TUTV News Gen. Colin Powell Press Conference, 2000-11-02; UA252.006.033.00015; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Tufts "Bubs" on David Letterman, undated; UA252.006.033.00016; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Jamshed Bharucha, Tufts University, 2003-11-26; UA252.006.033.00017; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - E-Bay, 2002-10-30; UA252.006.033.00018; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Tom McGurty - Costs of College, 2005-06-02; UA252.006.033.00019; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Tufts Veterinary School - Legs Broken, 2003-12-31; UA252.006.033.00020; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Tufts Commencement Tape #2, undated; UA252.006.033.00021; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Nalin Ambady, Harvard University, 2004-02-06; UA252.006.033.00022; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Tony Vaux - Women Responding to Disasters, 2003-10-20; UA252.006.033.00023; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)
  - Happy 150th, 2002-05-08; UA252.006.033.00024; 1 Video Recordings (Box 33)